Reid Campbell

Junior Web Developer

I earned my Bachelor's degree in Marketing, Advertising and Branding from the University of Gloucestershire in 2017 and worked in Sales and Digital Marketing positions since then.

In 2019, after quite some time considering it, I finally took the time to learn to code and completed the Web Development Bootcamp at Le Wagon London. Today my goal is joining an ambitious team and building products people love.

reidscottcampbell@gmail.com 🔀

07410500200 📞

London O

reidscottcampbell.co.uk

reidscottcampbell in

github.com/ReidCampbell (

WORK EXPERIENCE

Biddable Performance Executive

OMD

08/2018 - 04/2019

London

OMD is the world's largest media network with more than 12,000 people working in over 100 countries.

- Expanded depth of knowledge within the marketing sector. Applied and grew this breadth of knowledge, assisting and managing clients from a variety of industries and sectors including NSPCC & Mercedes.
- Took ownership of account structures and development using various bid management tools.
- Daily tasks included creative copy writing, planning outcomes based on prior performance, creation of bookings on native platforms (i.e. AdWords), reconciliation of budgets and management across platforms, and creation of weekly reports, including commentary.

Strategic Solutions Sales Coordinator JCDecaux

03/2018 - 08/2018

London

JCDecaux is the UK's number one out-of-home advertising company, part of the world's leading outdoor advertising company.

- Provided sales support to a busy airport sales team.
- Using key insights from market research and competitor activity, produced engaging sales presentations.
- Conducted regular industry research and provided lead generation.
- Other skills included organising client events, administrating temporary airport passes, and preparing and distributing of site availability.

Co-Founder

Beehive Basement Media

07/2017 - 06/2018

International

Beehive Basement Media is a media production and marketing agency founded in Hanoi, Vietnam.

- Skills within the company included photography, videography, editing, marketing and account management.
- Demonstrated excellent organisation skills as often working on many projects at once, sourcing and working directly with clients.
- Developed strong problem-solving skills and the ability to manage problems on a day to day basis and offering solutions with a proactive 'can do' attitude.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technologies:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ruby

Frameworks / Libraries:

React, Gatsby, React Native, Node, Express, Rails

Other:

TDD, Adobe Creative Suite, Git

Database:

SQL, GraphQL, MongoDB

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development

Le Wagon Coding Bootcamp

2019

10-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails. Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB.

BA Hons in Marketing, Advertising & Branding

University of Gloucestershire

2014 - 2017

PROJECTS

Gatsby Tours

gatsbytours.netlify.com

2:1

Travel website created with GatsbyJS and GraphQL.

brunchee.

www.brunchee.rocks

- Brunchee is a custom aggregator site to discover the best brunch venues in London.
- Brunchee was built on Ruby on Rails.

Find more at https://github.com/ReidCampbell

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Photographer/Videographer

Better Life Vietnam

08/2012 - 01/2016

Hanoi, Vietnam

A Non-governmental organization(NGO) with an aim of working to improve education conditions for underprivileged children in Vietnam

- Photographed and shot short documentaries about the families of potential scholarship receivers.
- Participated in award ceremony for scholarship receivers.
- Aimed to solve the shortage of books in rural areas, promote a reading culture, and enrich knowledge